To use all available functions on this website, JavaScript must be enabled in your browser.

GLOBAL

* [Menu](javascript:void(0);)

[](javascript:void(0);)

    Through Perfecting the Air, Daikin strives to make the world’s spaces happier and more comfortable.

* [
    
    * 100 Years of  
        Perfecting the Air](https://www.daikin.com/air/future)
* [
    
    * The Power to Create  
        the Air of the Future](https://www.daikin.com/air/elements)
* [
    
    * The Ideal Air by Daikin](https://www.daikin.com/air/ideal_air)

* Design & Technology

    Daikin leverages its experience and technology to deliver air conditioning solutions that meet the demands of any setting.

Products

    Pioneering Fluorine Technology Providing Solutions for Life

    Utilizing IPM motor and inverter technology for greater energy savings

* [
    
    * What is People-Centered Management?](https://www.daikin.com/careers/management)

PERFECTING THE AIR

ABOUT DAIKIN

PRODUCTS & SERVICES

SUSTAINABILITY

CAREERS

* Search

1. [Top](https://www.daikin.com/)
2. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Daikin Industries, Ltd. (hereinafter, "Daikin", "we", "us" etc. ), together with our group companies, is sincerely committed to ethical behavior and legal compliance, and we also consider the protection of personal information - a valuable asset entrusted to us - as our social responsibility, therefore, hereby we set forth this Privacy Policy.

1\. HANDLING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
------------------------------------

1. 1)
    
    Collection of Personal Information

Daikin time to time and to the extent necessary for legitimate business activities collects personal information during the course of our various business activities - such as air conditioning, chemical, oil hydraulics, defense and electronics business – through requests or contacts to us such as in relation to product or service orders, technical consultations, service or maintenance request or requests for catalogues and manuals etc, market or other surveys and events, and other requests.  
You can refer to our main products and services [here](https://www.daikin.com/products).

1. 2)
    
    Purpose of Processing Personal Information

We process the collected personal information for the following purposes.

Personal information of our Customers

1. (1)
    
    Supplying our products and services
    
2. (2)
    
    After sales and services
    
3. (3)
    
    Improving the quality of the planning/research and development of our products
    
4. (4)
    
    Responding to requests from our Customers
    
5. (5)
    
    Providing information about our products and/or services
    
6. (6)
    
    Organization of our sales campaigns and other events (e.g. sending out invitations)
    
7. (7)
    
    Surveys and product monitors
    
8. (8)
    
    Management of the access to our premises
    
9. (9)
    
    Advertising and sales promotion activities (including analyzing the collected information such as browsing history and purchase history and use such information for advertising, promotion and marketing purposes with respect to new products and services suited to the individual’s tastes and preferences)

Personal information of our Business Partners

1. (1)
    
    Organization of business meeting (e.g. sending out invitations)
    
2. (2)
    
    Contacts and provision of information to the persons in charge of our Business Partners
    
3. (3)
    
    Performance of works and services entrusted to us by our Business Partners
    
4. (4)
    
    Management of access to our premises

Personal information of our Shareholders

1. (1)
    
    Performance of our and our Shareholders' rights and obligations as prescribed by the Companies Act
    
2. (2)
    
    Provision of services to our Shareholders
    
3. (3)
    
    Management of shares and shareholders by preparing databases required by laws and regulations

Personal information of Applicants for Employment or Internships and Retired Employees

1. (1)
    
    Provision of information to Applicants for Employment or Internships and other human resources management related activities
    
2. (2)
    
    Management of hiring processes
    
3. (3)
    
    Provision of information to our Retired Employees

We may acquire from a third party personal information such as attribute information (e.g. age, gender, occupation, residence), cookies, IP addresses, advertising identifiers, location information, activity history, purchasing history, etc. that does not constitute personal information by itself, and we may use such such information by linking to personal information we already have. In such cases, we will use such personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

2.   
    
3. 3)
    
    Joint Use of Personal Information

Daikin may, within the scope of the above described purposes, jointly use the collected personal information with our group companies. The categories of personal information to be jointly used, the scope of data subjects, the purpose of use by the joint user, and the person who has the management responsibility are as follows. When the joint use is with third parties outside the Daikin group companies, we will inform the data subject about the scope, purpose and other necessary items via our website or by other means. 

1. (1)
    
    Categories of jointly used personal information  
    Name, address, phone and other contact information, other personal information for the above prescribed purposes including sales information related to our products/services, installation or maintenance related information etc.
    
2. (2)
    
    Entities jointly using the personal information  
    
3. (3)
    
    Purpose of use for joint users  
    We use personal information only to the extent necessary to achieve the purpose stated under 1.2 herein ("Purpose of Processing Personal Information”) or the purpose of use notified or announced by Daikin at the time of collection.
    
4. (4)
    
    Responsible entity  
    Daikin Industries, Ltd.

1. 4)
    
    Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

To the extent necessary for the purpose of processing personal information,Daikin may disclose personal information to our subcontractors. In addition, disclosure to third parties without the data subject's consent may occur in cases prescribed by law.

1. 5)
    
    Period for Storing Personal Information

Daikin stores personal information for the period necessary to achieve the purpose of obtaining the personal information, provided, however, that if laws require differently, such period will be set in accordance with the laws.

1. 6)
    
    Request for Disclosure etc of Personal Information

Upon receipt of request from the respective data subject pursuant to our procedures, Daikin will promptly disclose the personal information held by us about the data subject, unless such disclosure may cause major detrimental impact on our operations, and/or unless such disclosure may cause a risk to the life, safety, property or other rights of individual(s) etc.  
Furthermore, upon receipt of request from the respective data subject pursuant to our procedures in order to revise, add, delete or cease using personal information held by us on him or her, Daikin will promptly investigate the request, and in case the request is reasonable, we will certainly accept the request.

1. 7)
    
    Cross-border transfer

In cases when we transfer personal information across borders to our group companies or to third parties, we check applicable laws and regulations to such international transfer and comply with those laws and regulations.

2\. COMPLIANCE WITH LAWS ON THE PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
------------------------------------------------------------------

Daikin will comply with this Privacy Policy, our other internal rules, and applicable laws and guidelines on the protection of personal information.

3\. SECURITY MEASURES TO PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------------

Daikin has a management system and implements appropriate security measures in order to maintain integrity and security and prevent unauthorized access, loss, manipulation or leaks etc of personal information. Furthermore, upon subcontracting the processing of personal information, we make efforts to protect such personal information by selecting subcontractors who handle personal information appropriately and by prescribing the necessary measures to the subcontractor for the appropriate data management. In addition, when handling personal information in a foreign country, we take security measures after investigating and understanding the system of personal information protection in that country.

4\. CONTINUOUS IMPROVEMENT
--------------------------

Daikin regularly reviews and seeks to improve our efforts on the protection of personal information.

5\. COOKIES
-----------

Our policy with respect to the use of cookies are described [here](https://www.daikin.com/terms).

6\. PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION OF EUROPEAN UNION RESIDENTS
---------------------------------------------------------------

With regard to the personal data of the data subject residing in the European Union, Daikin will properly respond to requests from data subjects based on the right of access to the personal data, the right to correction, addition or erasure, the right to discontinuation of use, the right to data portability, the right to object, the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, and the right to withdraw consent.  
Daikin Group may transfer personal data of European Union residents to countries not recognized by the EU Commission as a country having an adequate level of protection; however, in such case, Daikin and Daikin Group companies will appropriately handle such personal data of EU residents in accordance with the appropriate safeguards set forth in General Data Protection Regulation (e.g. upon conclusion of Standard Contractual Clauses, and other adequatesafeguards).  
Furthermore, please note that data subjects residing in the European Union may lodge complaints to the supervisory authority with regard to the processing of personal data by Daikin.

[Procedures of the right to disclosure etc. are described here:](https://www.daikin.com/privacy/disclosure)  
[Procedures of the right to data portability, the right to object, the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, and the right to withdraw consent are described here:（104KB）](https://www.daikin.com/-/media/Project/Daikin/daikin_com/privacy/pdf/European_Union_Personal_Data_Rights_Request_Form_EN-pdf.pdf?rev=-1&hash=65776ECE02525922F2290B0B17A4F1A3)

7\. COMPLAINTS, CONTACTS
------------------------

Questions or complaints on our handling of personal information may be sent to this [contact:](https://www.daikin.com/contact/privacy)

Person responsible for processing personal information in Daikin Group is as follows:  
Osaka Umeda Twin Towers South,1-13-1 Umeda,Kita-ku,Osaka, Japan 530-0001  
Daikin Industries, Ltd. Attn: Global Data Protection Officer

Find out more in your region.

* DESIGN & TECHNOLOGY

LATEST NEWS

©DAIKIN INDUSTRIES, Ltd., 2024
